http://www.havasunews.com/site/privacy.html

Lake Havasu City, AZ
(86403)
Today
Clear skies. Low 49F. Winds SE at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
Clear skies. Low 49F. Winds SE at 5 to 10 mph.
Home
This policy explains how TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD may collect, use and aggregate personal information about you on WWW.HAVASUNEWS.COM. TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD respects your personal privacy and is committed to protecting it.If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD in one of the following ways:Mailing Address:TODAY'S NEWS-HERALDP.O. Box N/A2225 W. Acoma Boulevard,Lake Havasu City, Arizona 86403Phone: 928-453-4237E-mail: quinn@havasunews.comFor each visitor to the WWW.HAVASUNEWS.COM site, TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD's servers automatically collect information about which pages are visited and the IP address or domain name of visitors. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information but is used to gather broad demographic information. This information helps us tailor and improve your experience on the Web Site.Information we collectGeneral: Portions of TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD require visitors to provide personally identifiable information that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your consumer-buying habits. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.Surveys: We conduct periodic online surveys. For example, visitors to WWW.HAVASUNEWS.COM may see a pop-up window asking them to voluntarily participate in a user survey.Web site usage: We automatically collect IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit our site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our web sites on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, the length of their visits, their browser type and their operating systems.How we use information that is collectedTODAY'S NEWS-HERALD may use information collected from visitors in the following ways:    * To improve existing features or develop new features, products and services by analyzing how site features are being used.    * To award prizes in contests or promotions. Participation in some contests or promotions may require visitors to agree to be contacted by TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD.    * To provide advertisers or other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. Personally identifiable information is kept private and not distributed to third parties.    * To send e-mail notifications about new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. These contacts are on an opt-in basis only, based on the preferences you have specified with TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD.Children/direct notice to parentsTODAY'S NEWS-HERALD will not knowingly collect any personal information from individuals under 13 years of age without parental consent. Where appropriate, TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our site and/or will take reasonable steps to ensure parental consent to such submission.Parental consent will be required in the event TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD provides a feature or event such as a contest or promotion that requires submission of information by children. Notice may be provided in a number of ways, including sending an e-mail message or notice by postal mail. At any time, you may write to us at quinn@havasunews.com to request a summary of any information we have retained as part of such activities or to ask that it be deleted.Parents should be aware that TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD's Privacy Policy will govern our use of personal data, but that information which is voluntarily given by children (or others) in chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited mail. TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the Internet.CookiesTODAY'S NEWS-HERALD may place a "cookie"; on the browser of your computer. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common in the Internet industry, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features to their customers. The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information, but may be used to tell when your computer has contacted the TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD site. TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD uses the information for editorial purposes and for other purposes such as delivery of features and advertisements, so that TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD can customize delivery of information specific to your interests without compromising privacy. For example, cookies may be used to ensure that you will not see the same ads too often in a single session. We also may use cookies to save your passwords so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit portions of our site.RegistrationTODAY'S NEWS-HERALD requires voluntary registration. These forms require you to give us personally identifiable information, which may include contact information (like your name and e-mail address) and unique identifiers. If you so signify beforehand, we may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. Unique identifiers are collected only for use as account numbers in our record system. We do not disclose any unique identifiers to any third parties.The information collected from these registration forms is used to improve existing features or develop new features, products and services by analyzing how site features are being used. Such information may be shared with third parties on an aggregate basis.Demographic and profile dataWe also may collect demographic and profile data from you as part of the registration process (i.e., your ZIP code, sex, income level, interest in certain topics). We may use this data to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in, displaying the content according to your preferences and informing you of upcoming events on our site. We also share certain demographic and profile data with advertisers and business partners on an aggregated basis.TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD will disclose account information only in special cases, such as (i) to comply with valid legal requirements, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (ii) when TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or harm to TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD users or other persons or violating the Terms of Service of this site.LinksThis site contains links to other sites. TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, including any sites that may indicate a special relationship or partnership with TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD (such as co-branded pages and "powered by" relationships) or the sites of TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD advertisers that you go to by clicking on a banner ad on the WWW.HAVASUNEWS.COM site. TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD does not disclose unique identifiers to those responsible for the linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect personal information from you when you link to their site. This collecting of information is not subject to TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD's control. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policy of the sites you visit by linking from our Web Site.AdvertisementsWe display advertisements on our Web Site. These ads may contain cookies. We do not have access to this information, nor do we control its use. TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD does not provide any personally identifiable data regarding users to our advertisers.SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.E-mail NoticesTODAY'S NEWS-HERALD sends a variety of e-mails to registered users who post listings. These e-mails include but are not limited to confirmations that a listing has been posted, notices that the listing is about to expire, and notices that the listing has been deleted by an administrator. These e-mails are a necessary feature for TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD. If you do not want to receive such e-mail notices, please do not post a listing in TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD.Your role in protecting your privacyIf you share a computer terminal with others, you may want to consider establishing an anonymous e-mail account. In this way, e-mails that you receive from TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD, such as password reminders, will be seen only by you. If you access TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD through an e-mail account maintained by your employer, please note that it is possible that your employer may monitor your e-mail communications.Notification of changesThis Privacy Statement may be revised over time as new features are added to TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD or as Internet security and privacy standards evolve. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Statement each time you use TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD, in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.Correcting and updating informationTODAY'S NEWS-HERALD also permits you to correct or update personally identifiable information that you have previously provided to us. To do so, submit the changes directly through the site feature in question or send e-mail to: quinn@havasunews.com indicating the information that you wish to be corrected or updated.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this site, you signify your acceptance of the terms of TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD site and exit the site immediately. Your continued use of the WWW.HAVASUNEWS.COM site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of the TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD site, or your dealings with TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD, you can contact us at any time by sending electronic mail to quinn@havasunews.com, or by sending a letter delivered by first class postage prepaid U.S. mail or overnight courier to the following address:Mailing Address:TODAY'S NEWS-HERALD2225 W. Acoma Boulevard,Lake Havasu City, Arizona 86403Phone: 928-453-4237Copyright © 2012 Today's News-Herald
Search
Talkabout
Trend
Gallery
Videos
Comments
ArticlesLucky local takes home $1.25M on lottery ticket
California man arrested in bizarre case of unlawful imprisonment, bribery
Legal pot on the agenda for Havasu City Council
‘We Will Not Comply’ protest draws a crowd in Kingman
Christmas boat parade to launch with full participation Saturday
Gallery
Videos
Commented66 percent arrested during the weekend were Californians
(380)
Thousands participate in pro-Trump boat parade in Lake Havasu City (266)
Face masks required in Havasu starting Friday (242)
Local illegal immigrant arrests spike, while border migration declines
(203)
City to mull leave for Kaffenberger
(200)
Police shoot man at local motel
(180)
Cracks beginning to emerge from some in President Trump’s base in Mohave County (167)
Trump supporters to gather on Lake Havasu Saturday (160)
MotoCop takes to the streets of Havasu
(154)
ONLINE EXTRA: Havasu teen dies after struck by car
(146)
More calendar listings
